{
  "qcm": [
    {
      "id": "Q1",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "highway/motorway",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "autoroute"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q2",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "cool",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "frais"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q3",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "a smell",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "une odeur"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q4",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "to shimmer",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "vasciller"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q5",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "sight",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "la vue"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q6",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "dim",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "faible"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q7",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "to grow/grew/grown",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "devenir"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q8",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "to light up/lit/lit",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "allumer"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q9",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "a candle",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "une bougie"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q10",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "a corridor",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "un couloir"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q11",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "anytime of year",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "a n'importe quel moment de l'année"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q12",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "twisted",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "accro à"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q13",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "sweet",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "doux"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q14",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "sweat",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "transpiration"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q15",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "to remember",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "se rappeler"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q16",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "to forget/forgot/forgotten",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "oublier"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q17",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "to live up",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "mener la grande vie"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q18",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "ceiling",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "plafond"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q19",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "of our own device",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "de notre volonté"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q20",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "to gather",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "rassembler"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q21",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "to stab",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "poignarder"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q22",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "steel/steely",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "acier"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q23",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "to check out",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "payer la note"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q24",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "rely on",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "compter sur"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q25",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "unfortunately",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "malheuresement"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q26",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "elderly,old",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "vieux"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q27",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "available",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "disponible"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q28",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "to set",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "fixer"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q29",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "frail",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "faible"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q30",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "size",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "taille"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q31",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "understudy",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "une doublure"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q32",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "to pick, to select",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "choisir, sélectionner"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q33",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "the wings",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "les coulisses"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q34",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "although",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "bien que"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q35",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "authentication",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "authentification"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q36",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "header",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "un en-tête"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q37",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "currently",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "actuellement"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q38",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "match",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "égaler, correspondre"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q39",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "length",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "longueur"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q40",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "to state",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "énoncer, exposer, indiquer"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q41",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "unavailable",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "non disponible"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q42",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "checksum",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "somme de contrôle"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q43",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "even if",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "même si"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q44",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "keep alive",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "préserver, garder"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q45",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "share",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "partager"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q46",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "to glitter",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "briller, scintiller"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q47",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "all that glitters is not gold",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "tout ce qui brille n'est pas or"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q48",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "stairway",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "escalier"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q49",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "a store",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "un magasin"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q50",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "to get/got/got",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "arriver"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q51",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "to mean/meant/meant",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "vouloir dire, signifier"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q52",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "a meaning",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "un sens"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q53",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "a brook",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "un ruisseau"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q54",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "to think/thought/thought",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "penser"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q55",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "a thought",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "une pensée"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q56",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "misgiven",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "plein de doutes"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q57",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "to wonder",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "se demander"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q58",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "a ring",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "un anneau"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q59",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "smoke",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "la fumée"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q60",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "to whisper",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "murmurer"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q61",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "to dawn",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "se lever"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q62",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "dawn",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "aube"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q63",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "dusk",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "crépuscule"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q64",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "from dawn to dusk",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "du matin au soir"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q65",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "to laugh",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "rire"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q66",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "laughter",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "un rire"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q67",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "bustle",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "remu-ménage"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q68",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "a hedgerow",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "une haie"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q69",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "a path",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "un chemin"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q70",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "to hum",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "bourdonner"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q71",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "to blow/blew/blown",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "souffler"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q72",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "a shadow",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "une ombre"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q73",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "at last/at least",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "enfin/au moins"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q74",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "a tune",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "un air"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q75",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "to sing another tune",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "changer de ton"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q76",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "spring clean",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "nettoyage de printemps"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q77",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "to lie",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "mentir"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q78",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "to lie/lay/lain",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "se reposer"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q79",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "troubleshoot",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "dépanner"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q80",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "to intend",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "avoir l'intention de"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q81",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "further",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "plus loin"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q82",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "to ensure",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "s'assurer de"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q83",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "otherwise",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "autrement"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q84",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "to achieve",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "atteindre"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q85",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "previous",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "précédent"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q86",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "mastery",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "maitrise"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q87",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "to switch",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "commuter"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q88",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "backbone",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "épine dorsale"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q89",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "neither... nor",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "ni... ni"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q90",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "therefore",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "donc, alors"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q91",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "to outline",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "esquisser"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q92",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "goal, purpose",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "but"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q93",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "acknowledgement",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "reconnaissance, constatation"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q94",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "anything else",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "quoi que ce soit d'autre"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q95",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "knowledge",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "connaissance"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q96",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "major",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "principal"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q97",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "to have trouble",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "avoir des difficultés"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q98",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "to assume",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "présumer, supposer"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q99",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "self-assessment",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "auto évaluation"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q100",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "neighbor",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "voisin"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q101",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "to guess",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "deviner"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q102",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "flood",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "inonder, noyer"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q103",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "forwarding",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "faire suivre, expédier"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q104",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "whenever",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "à chaque fois que"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q105",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "already",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "déjà"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q106",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "to skew",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "biaiser"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q107",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "to drop",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "lâcher, abandonner"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q108",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "remote",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "à distance"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q109",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "to deal with",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "parler de"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q110",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "to provide",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "donner, fournir"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q111",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "comprehension, understanding",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "compréhension"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q112",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "there is no need",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "ce n'est pas la peine"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q113",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "how often",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "avec quelle fréquence"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q114",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "within",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "au sein de"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q115",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "to gauge",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "mesurer, évaluer"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q116",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "share",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "partager"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q117",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "reply, response",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "réponse"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q118",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "to override",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "réponse"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q119",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "to gather",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "rassembler"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q120",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "to prevent from",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "empêcher de faire"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q121",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "to perform",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "effectuer"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q122",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "two ways",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "à double sens"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q123",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "also",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "aussi"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q124",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "stage",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "étage"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q125",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "either... or",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "ou... ou"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q126",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "as such",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "en tant que tel"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q127",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "bandwidth",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "largeur de bande"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q128",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "feature",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "caractéristique"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q129",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "to belong",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "appartenir"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q130",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "fail",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "échouer, tomber en panne"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q131",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "relationship",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "relation"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q132",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "none",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "aucun"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q133",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "to interrelate",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "entrer en relation"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q134",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "efficient",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "efficace"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q135",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "each",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "chaque"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q136",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "own",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "propre, à soi"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q137",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "straightforward",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "simple, franc"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q138",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "so that",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "pour que, afin que"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q139",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "fully",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "totalement"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q140",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "prompt",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "provoquer"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q141",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "accurate",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "précis, fidèle, exact"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q142",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "prune",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "tailler, élaguer, réduire"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q143",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "while",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "pendant que"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q144",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "summarize",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "résumer"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q145",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "awaiting",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "être en attente"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q146",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "the next few chapters",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "les quelques chapitres suivants"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q147",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "obvious",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "évident"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q148",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "conversely",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "inversement, réciproquement"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q149",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "SPF",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "Shortest Path First"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q150",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "OSPF",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "Open Shortest Path First"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q151",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "LAN",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "Local Area Network"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q152",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "WAN",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "Wide Area Network"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q153",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "LSA",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "Link State Advertisement"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q154",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "LSU",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "Link State Update"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q155",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "LSR",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "Link State Request"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q156",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "LSP",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "Link State Packet"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q157",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "DR",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "Designated Router"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q158",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "BDR",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "Backup Designated Router"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q159",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "NBMA",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "Nonbroadcast multiaccess"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q160",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "DBD",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "Data Base Descriptor"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q161",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "DDP",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "Database Descriptor Packet"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q162",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "IP",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "Internet Protocol"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q163",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "CPU",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "Central Processing Unit"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q164",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "PVC",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "Permanent Virtual Circuit"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q165",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "HDLC",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "High level Data Link Control"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q166",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "FDDI",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "Fiber Distributed Data Interface"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q167",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "RFC",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "Request For Comment"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q168",
      "type": 1,
      "question": "IOS",
      "options": "",
      "correct_answer": "Input/Ouput System"
    }
  ]
}